Your values are kind of like your inner cheerleader.
They motivate you to do the things you care about.
Your values represent what you think is most important in life.
So let's take a closer look at that inner cheerleader.
Now this is important.
Why you ask?
Because your values help shape all of your financial decisions.
What material things are important to you?
How much money will you need?
And how will you earn that money?
Your values affect these decisions.
But what influences our values?
Our family, teachers, and friends play a big role
in determining our values.
Movies, music, and culture can make an impact too.
Your value set is made up of a number of factors.
Let's picture a big value web.
Everyone's will look different.
This is a big web.
These values influence your financial decisions.
Do you want a budget for a gym membership?
Own an electric bike or maybe a motorbike?
Do you want a budget for basketball tickets?
Or maybe you're a fan of the symphony?